{
    "id": "c5e32f964aab42ca90b187c62eec7bd2",
    "title": "Phrasal Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The car broke ………………………. at the most inopportune time.",
            "description": "When things break down, they stop working.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "down",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c7353aa9df2e4954a04300d6284bbe60"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will call you ………………………. in the afternoon.",
            "description": "To call someone back is to return a call.",
            "answers": [
                "back",
                "off",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b7a20c1192094e588d76e2c9f53eb34d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Talk to him after he has calmed ……………………… a bit.",
            "description": "To calm down is to become less upset or angry.",
            "answers": [
                "off",
                "in",
                "down"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e4f70bc22b6f44c5bc481cd0d6b1a9b0"
        },
        {
            "question": "I desperately need someone to cheer me …………………………",
            "description": "To cheer someone up is to make them happy. ",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "on",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e9d40f12141a4d64a731e62c1017e539"
        },
        {
            "question": "She did ………………………. the buttons on her jacket.",
            "description": "To do something up is to fasten it.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "out",
                "up"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "28612d78bec84d8b888a765047b5ae2b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I tripped on a bag and fell ……………………..",
            "description": "To fall over is to fall to the ground.",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "on",
                "out"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "775c4d36ae064258a2477179017c07df"
        },
        {
            "question": "Fill ………………………… the form before sending it.",
            "description": "To fill out a form is to write information in the spaces on a form.",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "out",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d848e098c0d644c4bdf6debd945b9eb1"
        },
        {
            "question": "It took me a long time to get ………………………. the loss.",
            "description": "To get over something is to start feeling better again.",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "over",
                "off"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9dd1d8db5ef740a29d063cd69e6b4085"
        },
        {
            "question": "We will not give ………………………. to their demands.",
            "description": "To give in is to agree to do something although you are not interested in it. ",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "up",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b125307506414134a8914fe0eff0fd55"
        },
        {
            "question": "Although she failed many times, she never thought of giving ……………………….",
            "description": "To give up is to stop doing something",
            "answers": [
                "in",
                "up",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4cdfc5052c2a498897e6b900c4ebaede"
        },
        {
            "question": "She kept …………………… talking about her problems.",
            "description": "To keep on doing something is to continue doing it. ",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "on",
                "over"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fa259af526f04a60a310a0ca3f22cfde"
        },
        {
            "question": "Why did you leave him ……………………….?",
            "description": "To leave somebody out is to not include someone.",
            "answers": [
                "up",
                "out",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9cc557bcffe74843b0dc85ab857f0a06"
        }
    ]
}